Another group? Yes.
They arrived just before your
party did. Now have a seat.
Thank you for having us.
Huh? What's the matter
with you three?
Aren't you going
to come and join us?
Careful, Han. Huh?
But why? It isn't
proper for fairies to eat
in front of people.
That's silly. We always
eat together, don't we? Huh?
Yes, but we aren't
the only ones here.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but can the fairies sit down?
We've been dining
together this whole trip.
Well. That depends. It certainly
isn't a problem for me.
But I wouldn't want
to offend the other guests.
Let them sit.
We don't mind at all.
Hello, young miss. And what's
your name? It's an Anne Halford.
My name's Hugh. And don't worry
about etiquette. Do as you like.
I see
you're off to Lewiston. That's
why you're taking
the bloody highway.
Exactly. That's where the sugar
confectionery exhibition is.
And we plan to be there.
Oh, so you're
both sugar artisans, are you?
If that's the case,
then having two
labour fairies in a companion
fairy seems like overkill.
Chow's a warrior fairy, not a
companion fairy. He's protecting me.
That's a warrior fairy.
What a joke! I'm not.
Joking. Don't worry.
There's no need to be
embarrassed with good
looks like that.
I see why it appeals to you.
Is that why you brought
that fairy here? Attraction.
That, isn't it? All right,
then, let's test it out.
Not bad. Do you desire to be
killed? Unfortunately,
I'm not that broken.
Stand down. Salim. That's
enough. The matter with you?
Are you a fool? If you harm
someone in my group,
then you'll pay for it.
Sorry about that.
It's just hard to believe
something that beautiful
is a warrior fairy.
It's hardly a good reason.
Come on now.
I said I was sorry. Let's see.
How about I cover
the cost of your
stay? Does that make us even?
Don't try to buy me off.
Wait. Are you serious?
Sure. For all five of you.
Though
I feel like I'll
be taking a loss if I do.
I know, how's this? Make me
some sugar confections, huh? Mm.
Just two.
About the size of your fist.
If you do that, you can stay
for free. What do you say?
That sounds fair,
but you can't back out on us.
Jonas,
will you get two bowls, please?
Oh, here. Thank you.
Are you sure
you should use
up that silver sugar?
You still have to make your piece
for the exhibition, don't you?
Yes,
but I'll have more than enough
left if I save
what's in these barrels.
You must have ambitious plans.
Then they
judge your sugar refining too, right?
I'm starting to get excited.
I can't
wait to show my skills in front
of all those people, I suppose.
Huh? And do you know
about the school I belong to?
Well, just between us,
I might get
a chance to become headmaster. The
Radcliffe workshop school. Mhm.
But obviously,
before I can do that,
I need to earn a Royal Medal
so I can prove I'm
a silver sugar master.
Then why don't you enter the
exhibition this time too? No.
This year I'm just spectating.
But I'll
do it at some point.
Don't you worry, Anne.
Otherwise, I can't then become
the silver sugar Viscount. Huh?
Did you say the Viscount Silver sugar
master to the Royal family?
I didn't realize
you wanted that.
Of course I do.
And I will achieve it.
Whatever it takes for a commoner
like me to become a noble.
What better future
could I hope for?
Which is why
I'd like for you to marry me
once.
I'm the silver sugar viscount. I
can make your life so happy.
I'm sorry. I have work to do.
I've got all
the equipment ready for you.
There's no need to color
your sugar confections.
I'll leave the form up to you, too.
I'm still confused.
Who are you? Are
you a sugar artisan as well?
If you want me to pay
for you to stay,
then you'd better get to work.
An.
What should I make?
Mama would take
advantage of the silver
sugar's natural color.
Mhm. Both of you are very proficient.
You definitely aren't novices. However.
What have you done? They were
ugly, so I destroyed them.
Jonas, you have skill,
but that's all you have.
You're so focused on showing off
your technique, you forget creativity.
You did better than him, Anne.
But something isn't right.
I get the feeling
you were simply
imitating someone else's
creation as an ape would do.
Sure, it's pretty,
but there's no charm to it.
If something doesn't change,
then your dreams
of being a silver sugar
master will never come true.
Still, it'd be a shame
to let these pieces go to waste.
We'll make a good snack.
Well, then, Anne Jonas,
this was a fun little
diversion while it lasted.
What was the point
of toying with you like that?
Please don't let it upset you,
Master Jonas.
That's right.
Anne, he's just being a bully.
Hey, wait! Please,
Anne, don't run away!
The caterpillars back.
What's so funny? Do you enjoy.
Seeing people when
they're upset? How can you look?
Someone's tears and laugh.
Oh, that's right, a scarecrow.
Like me is a joke
no matter what I do.
Humans don't spend their
whole lives as a joke.
Unlike my kind,
they are always changing.
For example, in just three years,
you will become startlingly beautiful.
Your hair will turn
to a lovely shade of pale gold,
and your skill with sugar confections will
change as well, you'll see.
I'm going to become
the best sugar artisan there is.
I'll show that man
what a fool he was.
But shall some things can't
be changed with hard work?
You don't have to lie
to make me feel better.
They aren't lies.
Believe me. When I was born,
the first thing I saw
was a human child.
A five year old girl whose hair
was the same color as yours.
The eyes that first brought
me to life were hers.
Her name was Elizabeth,
but I knew her as Liz.
She was the daughter
of nobles and for
certain reasons was
isolated from society.
Liz was young and knew
nothing of the world,
with no idea
that fairies existed.
Because of that, she mistook
me for her older brother.
She took me back to her
mansion and gave me shelter.
Soon 15 years passed.
Liz's hair turned
to pale gold,
her freckles faded.
She was a fine woman,
so I can tell
you'll keep changing as she did.
So, um, where is she now? Why
isn't she with you?
Did she go somewhere?
She died.
She was murdered by your kind.
I'm sorry.
Go to sleep, Scarecrow.
I wonder why that Hugh
fellow paid for our
stay even after what happened.
Hey, Anne. Hear me?
Chow said he wouldn't be
friends with a human,
but at the start of his life,
he had an emotional bond
with a human girl.
He spent the same amount of time
with her than I had with mama.
So in his eyes,
Liz might have been
like family and that was taken
from him by human hands.
Humans are the reason
his heart is frozen over.
It's cold, isn't it?
We fairies don't feel the cold,
so I couldn't say.
I wish there was magic
that could melt Shell's heart.
Perhaps I can help. I promised
him a sugar confection.
I'll make it right now.
Maybe it'll
warm his heart
even just a little.
What?
No. Why? The sugar is. Missing.
How could it have disappeared?
What's the matter? Are.
The silver sugar is gone.
Gone. I have three barrels left,
but I don't have what I need
to make my competition piece.
Anne. What's happening? Anne.
Apparently the silver
sugar she needs for
the exhibition is gone. What?
But I'm fairly certain it was
in the cargo hold,
and it was locked so
no one could get in or out.
No, there was a way in.
What are you saying, Kathy?
I saw it myself
the night we stayed
at the doctor's
in Nethra lid pod
came out of the cargo
hold of Mr. San's wagon.
He was covered in silver sugar.
I could
see him sparkling
in the moonlight.
Is that true?
What's going on? You're
all so loud.
Come down here, Mythril!
Hey, you can't give orders
to a fairy who isn't yours.
And you will address me
by my full name, Lord.
Come here now. Fine. What is it?
Anne. Silver sugar
has disappeared. And we all
know that you're
the one who stole
it. Oh, Kathy saw you herself.
That's not true.
She's lying. Please believe me.
And I didn't do anything.
Kathy's a liar.
And what would Kathy stand
to gain by framing you?
Look, you shut up.
Anne, you know it's a lie.
Don't you trust me?
I swear I never do that.
I owe.
And you are suspicious of me.
You really don't believe me? Am.
I wish I could.
And yet you still don't.
Fine. If you're gonna look
at me like I'm a thief,
then I'll just
disappear from your sight.
Goodbye and good riddance.
Wait, wait. Oh!
This is awful. How am I supposed
to enter the contest now?
I have an idea. If you only
need enough to build one piece,
then you can just make
that much silver sugar yourself.
Jonas, that requires
a lot of sugar apples.
Don't worry.
I know where we can find some.
I heard about it at a Radcliffe
workshop school gathering.
They say that there's
a grove of sugar
apple trees
on the bloody highway.
It takes three days
to refine silver sugar,
but if you add it to the amount
you already have,
you should be able to finish your
piece in time to participate.
There's so many.
The exhibitions in five days
and Lewiston isn't
too far after the
next fort shelter,
so we're saved.
He'll be fine.
Plus, I'm a trained
sugar artisan as well,
remember? I can help you.
Thanks a lot, Jonas. Let's go.
Here.
Um. Where's mithril? Not here.
You have any idea where he went?
Are you sure it was him? Did
he really take the silver sugar?
I don't know,
but to be honest with you,
I don't really care who took it.
Either way,
I'll make sure I finish in time.
Like I said, I have to enter
the competition this year.
Well, back to work.
For the exhibition, I'm going
to submit a sugar confection
that's designed for a special celebration.
Something large and beautiful.
Mama,
this is my life's fortune. An.
It cannot be copied
and it mustn't be given away.
I get the feeling
you were simply
imitating someone else's
creation as an ape would do.
Then what should I make?
I don't know what to do anymore.
Use this barrel to store
your silver sugar if you want.
It's a special one
that keeps humidity out.
Thanks, but I already have
two empty barrels here.
So you decided what to make?
You really are incredible, Anne.
I just know
your creation is going
to take everyone's breath away.
Let's hope you're right.
I have high hopes for you.
What's
happening? I love you, Anne.
Jonas.
What? Why? Listen,
I don't think of you that way.
I love you so much.
But that doesn't
mean you should do that.
I don't love you, Jonas.
I see. Ah. I was hoping you
would fall for me eventually, but.
I'm sorry, I just.
No. I'm sorry.
Allow me to give you
some advice, Mistress Anne.
Where is this coming from?
Should he propose
or say he loves you? Ignore it.
You cannot let
it go to your head.
Huh?
What I'm saying is, Master Jonas
would never fall in love with
the likes of you. Hey, Cathy.
I could be wrong,
but are you in love with Jonas?
Me in love with. That is
completely absurd. I see.
That's wonderful.
It's so nice to see
fairies and humans get together,
isn't it?
Huh? No. It's ridiculous.
I'm such an idiot.
The person Cathy's
in love with is
holding her wing.
Must be complicated.
Fairies and humans
falling in love. I
wonder if Xiao and Li's were.
How strange.
My chest feels tight. Anyway,
that's got nothing
to do with me.
The reason shell is with
me is because
I'm the one who holds his wing.
And once we get to Lewiston,
that's going to change.
I'm done.
It's perfect.
Except as an ape would do.
He's wrong. The technique was flawless.
It's fine. Everything's fine.
Have you finished?
It's drying now. I'll
grind up what's left
of the silver sugar.
And then let's see
if we leave tomorrow.
We'll get there a day
before the event.
You know,
the day that you and I met
at the ferry market,
you smelled of silver sugar.
But I didn't know why.
It was strange. Really.
I wonder if the scent
got into my dress.
Your hands. That sweet fragrance comes
from your hands. That's silly.
I'm certain of. It. Huh?
Well. All right then.
Anne. Anne, you're so amazing. You
finished your sugar confection?
I've never seen such
a large piece look so delicate.
They'll give you
the Royal Medal, for sure.
Thanks, Jonas.
You made it possible by
telling me
about the sugar apples.
Oh, no.
I should be thanking you. Huh?
Did you need something
out of my wagon?
I think we should get going now.
What's the hurry? The silver
sugar isn't done drying yet.
And shouldn't we switch
back to my horse first?
That's no problem.
My horse runs faster
than yours anyway. I don't know.
If you'd fallen in love
with me and married me,
I wouldn't have had
to do something
like this. It's all your fault.
What are you doing? See,
this is why I told you not to.
Let it go to your head.
What is that?
Oh, it smells terrible.
What's happening?
They lured them here. So they
could steal your sugar confection.
It can't be. Bye bye and ciao.
Go get Jonas. If I leave you
here. The wolves will kill you.
I don't care. Just go. So I'm
begging you to, I need you.
I refuse. You.
No matter what happens to me,
we can't let them take. Wait.